<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->
<testimonials>
    <testimonial img="1401196441463016508.png">
        <ru>
            <name>Mr. S.B</name>
            <city>Великобритания</city>
            <text>Я наслаждаюсь жизнью со своими новыми зубами, и конечно же должен поблагодарить вас за это. Нам понравилась поездка в Черногорию и хотелось бы больше по ней попутешествовать. Многие люди спрашивают меня о моих зубах, и, я надеюсь, что всегда даю им правильную информацию об имплантатах. В Великобритании люди очень недовольны стоматологами, и многие хотят знать о лечении в Европе. Я всегда рекомендую доктора Стэфана и показываю свои рентген. снимки и ваш веб-сайт. Я планирую поменять мой 1-й мост на постоянный из металло-керамики, но на данный момент я не могу найти времени для этого.</text>
        </ru>
        <en>
            <name>Mr. S.B</name>
            <city>UK</city>
            <text>I am enjoying life with my new teeth and of course I have to thank you for this. We enjoyed visiting Montenegro and would like to see more of the area.Many many people ask me about my teeth and I hope that I always give them the right information about implants - In the UK people are very dissatisfied with dentists and lot more people want to know about treatment in Europe . I always like to recommend Stefan and show them my Xrays and the website. I plan to exchange my 1st bridge for a final one from metal-ceramics, but at the moment I cannot find time for this.</text>
        </en>   
    </testimonial>
    <testimonial img="1401196441463016508.png">
        <ru>
            <name>Alex</name>
            <city>Великобритания</city>
            <text>Г-н Б. позвонил мне сегодня. Я уверен, что он опасается визита, особенно потому, что в первый раз. Я заверил его, что ему не нужно беспокоиться, особенно о вашей клинике. Он будет в руках экспертов, и его пребывание в Черногории будет запоминающимся по самым лучшим причинам.</text>
        </ru>
        <en>
            <name>Alex</name>
            <city>UK</city>
            <text>Mr B. telephoned me today. I am sure he is apprehensive about his visit, particularly because he has not done this before. I assured him that he has very little to worry about, in particular about your clinic. He will be in expert hands and his stay in Montenegro will be memorable for the best reasons. </text>
        </en>     
    </testimonial>
    <testimonial img="1401196441463016508.png">
        <ru>
            <name>Ольга</name>
            <city></city>
            <text>У моей мамы все хорошо и она очень довольна своими зубами! Мои родители рассказали мне много положительных вещей о вас. Спасибо, за заботу о них. Моя свекровь тоже думает о лечении.</text>
        </ru>
        <en>
            <name>Olga</name>
            <city></city>
            <text>My mother is doing well and very happy with her teeth! My parents told me many positive things about you. Thank for taking good care of them. My mother in law us thinking about it.</text>
        </en>  
    </testimonial>
    <testimonial img="020820181610.png">
        <ru>
            <name>Г-жа Х.С.</name>
            <city>Великобритания</city>
            <text>Мы только что вернулись из Нью-Йорка / Нью-Джерси, где провели семь недель с друзьями и родственниками. И без ваших специальных имплантатов моей жене не удалось бы насладиться такой поездкой. Она - новый человек и может с уверенностью общаться с людьми.</text>
        </ru>
        <en>
            <name>Mrs. H.S.</name>
            <city>UK</city>
            <text>We have just returned from seven weeks in New York/ New Jersey with friends and relatives. And without your special implants my wife would not have been able to enjoy such trips. She is a new person and is able to interact with people with confidence.</text>
        </en>      
    </testimonial>
    <testimonial img="020820181558.png">
        <ru>
            <name>Филл</name>
            <city>Австралия</city>
            <text>Просто хотел бы держать вас в курсе. Прошло уже более двух лет с тех пор, как вы и ваша специализированная команда провели полное восстановление моих зубных рядов и должен сказать, что это, безусловно, лучшее решение, которое я когда-либо делал относительно своего здоровья и благополучия. С тех пор как у меня появились новые зубы, я продолжаю наслаждаться жизнью без каких-либо проблем и полагаю, что вы можете использовать эту информацию для продвижения своей превосходной и профессиональной системы, чтобы другие могли избавиться от агонистических проблем, связанных с зубными проблемами. Еще раз спасибо вам обоим за прекрасный личный исход. Приветствия.</text>
        </ru>
        <en>
            <name>Phill</name>
            <city>Australia</city>
            <text>Just wanted to give you both a little feedback. It has now been over 2 years since you and your specialist team performed my full mouth dental implants and teeth and must say that it is by far the best decision I have ever made regarding my health and well being. Since my new teeth I have continued to enjoy life without any problems and trust that you are able to use this information to promote your excellent and professional system so that others can be relieved of the agonies of ongoing dental issues. Again thank you to you both for a wonderful personal outcome.</text>
        </en>   
    </testimonial>
    <testimonial img="1401196441463016508.png">
        <ru>
            <name>Phill</name>
            <city>N/A</city>
            <text>Я хотел бы просто поблагодарить вас и доктора Стэфана за полностью профессиональный подход к моему недавнему запланированному контрольному осмотру для обеспечения оптимального результата моего зубного ряда, восстановленного на имплантатах. Опять же, я благодарю вас обоих за прекрасную работу, молодецы. Я очень, очень счастливый клиент.</text>
        </ru>
        <en>
            <name>Phill</name>
            <city>N/A</city>
            <text>I would just like to say thank you very much to you and Stefan's totally professional approach to my recent programmed check up visit and ensuring that the optimum outcome of my full mouth dental implant replacement was achieved. Again, I thank you both for a wonderful job, well done. I am a very, very happy client.</text>
        </en> 
    </testimonial>
</testimonials>